{
    "subject": "resource/Agile_software_development",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Software_project_management",
    "human_readable": "Agile software development is about Software project management.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9262245297431946,
            "question": "How does Agile software development approach project management?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8032135963439941,
            "question": "How does Agile software development differ from traditional project management approaches?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7749291658401489,
            "question": "How can Agile software development be adapted to different types of projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6974096894264221,
            "question": "What is the focus of Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5543830394744873,
            "question": "What role does collaboration play in Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5424059629440308,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of Agile software development methodologies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5395692586898804,
            "question": "What benefits can be achieved by using Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5135188102722168,
            "question": "What are the key principles of Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48095327615737915,
            "question": "What is the future outlook for Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42569664120674133,
            "question": "What are some common challenges faced by teams implementing Agile software development?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Agile software development is about Software project management.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1589_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the future outlook for Agile software development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1589_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the key principles of Agile software development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1589_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What benefits can be achieved by using Agile software development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1589_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1589_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents discuss agile methodologies, both as a principle of project management and specifically for software development. The information supports that agile software development involves managing software projects using iterative processes and emphasizes collaboration and adaptability, which are key aspects of software project management."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}